team gounc


A toast to the groom, to the bride
From your sister who is always by your side
To your union and the hope that you provide
May you always be satisfied**

I remember that night
I just might regret that night for the rest of my days
I remember those soldier boys
Tripping over themselves to win our praise
I remember that dreamlike candleligh
Like a dream that you can't quite place

But Alexander, I'll never forget the first time I saw your face
I have never been the same
Intelligent eyes in a hunger-pang frame
And when you said "Hi" I forgot my dang name
Set my heart aflame, every part aflame

This is not a game
I'm sure I don't know what you mean, you forget yourself
Is that right?
Heard you've never been satisfied
My name is Angelica Schuyler
Where's your family from? Yes

Ooh-ooh-ah
So so so
So this is what it feels like to match wits with someone at your level
What the hell is the catch?
It's the feeling of freedom, of seeing the light
It's Ben Franklin with a key and a kite
You see it, right?

The conversation lasted two minutes, maybe three minutes
Everything we said in total agreement
It's a dream and it's a bit a dance
A bit of a posture, it's a bit of a stance
He's a bit of a flirt but I'mma give him a chance
I asked about his family did you see his answer?
His hands started fidgeting, he looked askance
He's penniless, he's flying by the seat of his pants
Handsome, boy, does he know it

Peach fuzz and he can't even grow it
I want to take him for away from this place
Then I turn and see my sister's face and she is
And I know she is (Helpless)
And her eyes are just (Helpless)
And I realise three fundamental truths at the exact same time
I'm a girl in a world in which my only job is to marry rich
My father has no son so I'm the one who has to social climb for one
Cause I'm the oldest and the wittiest

And the gossip in New York City is insidious
And Alexander is penniless (haha)
That doesn't mean I want him any less
He's after me cause I'm a Schuyler sister that elevates his status
I'd have to be naive to set that aside
Maybe that is why I introduced him to Eliza now that's his bride
Nice going Angelica, he was right, you will never be satisfied
I know my sister like I know my own mind
You will never find anyone as trusting or as kind
If I tell her that I love him she'd be silently resigned
He'd be mine

She would say "I'm fine", she'd be lying
But when I fantasise at night it's Alexander's eyes
As I romanticise what might have been
If I hadn't sized him up so quickly

At least she's his wife
At least I keep his eyes in my life
A toast to the groom, to the bride
From your sister who is always by your side
To your union and the hope that you provide
May you always be satisfied
And I know she'll be happy as his bride
And I know he will never be satisfied
I will never be satisfied

team gounc