Bittersweet

Can't believe it ends this way, thought you'd always stay
Now I gotta wonder what I changed
Think I have to go, walkin' all alone
Hate to see it all go down the drain
Wanted to be with you, wanted to make it through, but did you?
I swear I knew
Now that it's over, you blame it all on me
I know I should be bitter, but baby, right now I'm bittersweet
I'm gettin' over what you put me through
And I'd say I'm done cryin', but baby, I don't lie like you do (ha, ha)
You do (ha, ha), you do (ha, ha)
Right now I'm bittersweet (ha, ha)
Ooh (ha, ha), mm (ha, ha)
Right now I'm bittersweet
