Golden

[Verse 1]
**I was a ghost, I was alone (hah)
어두워진 앞길 속에 (hah)
Given the throne, I didn't know how to believe
I was the queen that I'm meant to be
I lived two lives, tried to play both sides
But I couldn't find my own place
Called a problem child 'cause I got too wild
But now that's how I'm getting paid 끝없이 on stage.**

[Chorus]
**I'm done hidin', now I'm shinin' like I'm born to be
We dreamin' hard, we came so far, now I'll believe
You know we're gonna be, gonna be golden
We're gonna be, gonna be
Born to be, born to be glowin'
밝게 빛나는 우린
You know that it's our time, no fears, no lies
That's who we're born to be.**


